The Swan Princess Christmas is a family, animation,
fantasy film directed by Richard Rich.
Princess Odette, Prince Derek and their trusted woodland friends reunite in this
all-new adventure for their first Christmas celebration together!
As the kingdom prepares for a festive holiday, the
villainous Rothbart plots to destroy Christmas.
Will the castle friends be able to stop Rothbart and save the day?
Told in beautiful CG animation for the very first time and featuring music by Anna Graceman from TV’s America’s Got
Talent, The Swan Princess Christmas is an enchanting musical holiday treat the whole family will enjoy!
Prince Derek (voice), played by Yuri Lowenthal.
Ferdinand the Chef (voice), played by Brian Nissen.
Maid (voice), played by Catherine Parks.
Number 9 / Footman (voice), played by David Lodge.
Lord Rogers (voice), played by Joseph Medrano.
Chamberlain (voice), played by James Arrington.
The Swan Princess is an animated film series that began with the 1994 film The Swan
Princess, loosely based on the 1877 ballet Swan Lake by Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky.
There are twelve films in the series.
The film explores themes of princess, kingdom, holiday, musical, sequel.